95: Alright, let's go!
Vista: Woah.
Vista: Is this a SUV?
98: Yep!
ME: Looks brand new!
98: I got this a while ago.
98: What do you guys think?
7: There's so much space.
7: I think you made a great choice!
Vista: I agree.
98: Thanks!
98: Let me start the engine.
ME: I figure you can carry 5 PCs in here.
98: I think it'd be more than that.
ME: Haha.
98: I’ll start driving now.
98: Let us begin!
XP: Picking up speed now!
Chicago: I think we’ll reach before 2 PM.
Chicago: The station isn't too far away.
XP: Great!
XP: What about the high speed train?
Chicago: I think that'd take 2 hours.
XP: Ah.
Ubuntu 6.06 LTS: I like taking time, honestly.
XP: Me too.
Longhorn: Same.
Chicago: No rush, anyway.
3.1: Yeah.
Ubuntu 6.06 LTS: Yeah.
Ubuntu 6.06 LTS: Oh yeah, how's the invention?
Chicago: Pretty good.
Ubuntu 6.06 LTS: Ah, glad to hear.
XP: What are you making?
Chicago: Pretty good.
Chicago: Nah, just kidding.
Chicago: I’m upgrading the asset replicator.
XP: Oh wow.
Ubuntu 6.06 LTS: Wow, good luck with that.
Chicago: Thanks.
Ubuntu 6.06 LTS: No problem.
OS X Leopard: I wonder how long it'll take to hike.
95: I think it'll take a day.
95: It's a lot more intensive.
OS X Leopard: Oh wow.
8: I can't wait!
2.0: Same.
OS X Leopard: Yeah.
OS X Leopard: I’ve never hiked this much before.
95: Well, this will be the biggest of all!
95: We’ll have tons of fun there.
OS X Tiger: Don't forget the surprise for 98.
95: Of course.
OS X Leopard: I wonder what he’ll think about it.
95: Same.
2.0: What did you guys buy?
95: Well, since he likes maniacal stuff…
95: I got him a PC running his system.
2.0: Hey, that's a nice gift.
2.0: I got him some floppy disks.
95: Oh wow, that’s a combination.
OS X Leopard: I agree.
OS X Leopard: I got him an old Macintosh.
95: Ah, you dare question the competition.
OS X Leopard: Oh no.
95: Haha!
95: Welp, we're here!
8: Looks like we're first.
95: I think we took the fastest route.
95: But the others should arrive soon.
8.1: Let's wait in the station, then.
98: Alright, let's go!
95: Wow!
95: This is new.
2.0: Picturesque renovation!
95: Agreed!
95: Let's go in.
95: It's here!
98: What?!
98: We're going on that???
95: Yep!
95: It's now in service here.
98: 95, I'm speechless.
98: I've always wanted to board this!
95: You're welcome!
Chicago: Too bad 1.0 isn't here, though.
95: Yeah, I hope he’s doing well.
98: I bet he's really busy after this.
95: I agree.
95: Well, let's start with something.
95: Allons-y, messeiurs?
7 & 98: Allons-y!
Chicago, XP, Vista, OS X Leopard: Ouais!
OS X Tiger & 8.1: En effet!
2.0, 8, Ubuntu 6.06 LTS: Oui!
98: Wow, this is beautiful!
95: I know right!
98: I've never been on a train like this before.
98: Thanks for all this, 95!
95: No problem.
98: Ah, it’s the old voice.
Chicago: Well, now I know that hasn't changed!
Chicago: That’s the best this train can have.
3.1: I know right.
3.1: This is nostalgic!
95: This is exciting!
98: I agree.
Vista: I can't wait for the hike!
7: Same!
Vista: I wonder how it's like there.
95: You'll see!
95: It's gonna be a surprise.
Chicago: Hey guys.
Chicago: Just for some nostalgia and fun...
Chicago: Anyone want to play my multiplayer Pinball?
98: The multiplayer one?
Chicago: Yep!
98: Ah, definitely!
95: You say it!
95: Although, how will everyone else play?
Chicago: I'll help set it up.
Chicago: Anyone else want to play?
Vista: I'm all for it.
7: Same.
8.1: Me too.
Longhorn: Same here.
Chicago: Alright.
Chicago: Let me set things up.
Chicago: Alright, let's start!
Chicago: Alright, it's my turn.
Chicago: I hope I get a better score this time!
98: Good luck!
Chicago: I didn't forget some controls this time.
95: Ah, I remember.
3.1: I think we all did.
95: Not sure how we forgot.
Chicago: Wow, that was close.
Vista: I know right.
98: It's been way too long since I played this.
7: I've barely played it.
Vista: Yeah, me neither.
Chicago: Wow, that was unexpected.
95: I remember I scored crazy there.
Chicago: Indeed.
Chicago: You annihilated our scores.
OS X Leopard: Woah, that was a save.
Chicago: Ack, nevermind.
Chicago: Welp, second shot!
Chicago: You annihilated our scores.
OS X Leopard: Another one!
Chicago: Nevermind again.
Chicago: Oh well.
Chicago: This is my last shot.
95: Woah.
Chicago: Wait, that's a neat trick.
Chicago: That was close!
Chicago: Noo!
Chicago: Oh well.
95: Hey, you got a better score.
Chicago: Yep.
95: Alright, my turn!
95: Oh wow.
95: Woah.
98: Hey, you're pretty good at this.
95: Thanks!
95: I've played this a fair amount.
98: Ah.
95: Ack.
95: Oh, what?
Vista: Wow, that was close.
95: Noo!
95: Oh well.
95: This is gonna be the last one.
XP: You guys are doing really good.
8: This is gonna be difficult for me, haha.
Ubuntu 6.06 LTS: Same, this is intensive.
95: Wow, back-to-back.
ME: I wonder what score 98's going to get.
98: Haha.
98: I haven't played this in a decade, though.
Chicago: Fair enough.
95: Oh, what?
95: What is going on?
Chicago: What was that?!
95: I don't know!
95: Ack, noo!
95: At least I did pretty good.
Chicago: You still beat me.
Chicago: Haha.
95: Oh well.
95: Let's see what 98 can do!
98: Alright.
95: Oh wow.
98: Haha.
Chicago: Two in a row!
XP: Woah.
95: That's another one!
3.1: What is going on?
95: Wait, what?!
Chicago: What just happened?!
98: Apparently the refueling gave me a bonus.
98: I barely read the description, though.
95: Me neither.
98: I'm really surprised...
7: I think we all are.
Vista: Massive understatement!
95: You are insane, 98.
Chicago: There's no way you're a maniac of this.
98: I mean, let's just say I was interested in the game.
ME: Equivalent enough!
98: Haha.
95: I should've known!
98: This is literally the fifth time I've re-entered.
Chicago: I know right.
98: I spoke too soon.
95: You just annihilated my score.
95: What have you done?
98: Ack.
95: And not a single fail!
ME: I think we can all confirm he's crazy with this.
Chicago: You don't say!
Longhorn: What is happening???
8.1: What is even going on?
98: 1 million!
7: Wow.
Vista: I can't comprehend this!
98: Ack.
95: What did I just see?
Chicago: I have no idea...
95: That was close.
98: Yeah.
98: Let's aim for 2 million.
95: I think you'll get more than that.
98: Let's see.
98: It's been over a decade since I played this.
95: Wait, what?
95: I'm going to faint.
98: Don't, haha.
98: This isn't the best I can do.
XP: I'm speechless.
OS X Tiger: Well, you've earnt my respect.
98: Thanks, everyone.
98: This isn't good.
95: You still have one more.
98: Yeah, let's hope I get there before I lose.
2.0: Come on...
98: That scared me for a second.
95: This is getting intensive.
Chicago: Close call...
Vista: Just a bit more!
98: Okay, that was scary!
95: You're almost there!!!
Chicago: Come on, you can do this!
98: What is happening?!
Ubuntu 6.06 LTS: Come on!
ME: You can do this!
95: 1.9 million!
Chicago: So close!
95: Noo!!!
98: We were so close!!!
98: Oh well...
Chicago: That was an amazing game.
98: I know right!
7: That was really good, 98!
98: Thanks!
7: No problem.
7: Oh, it looks like it's my turn now.
7: Let me start playing.
Vista: How are you so good at this?
98: Well, I played this game a lot.
98: Especially while I was on the earth.
98: I pretty much researched.
Vista: Oh wow.
Vista: I used to do that with Chess Titans.
98: Oh, nice!
ME: I remember 98 playing Pinball.
ME: I kept losing to him, haha.
98: Ah.
98: It’s crazy thinking it’s already been 20 years.
95: I can’t believe it, either.
95: Also, I should’ve known.
95: 98’s always been the king for this.
98: Haha, maybe.
98: You’re doing really good though.
95: Thanks.
ME: We’re almost there!
7: Can't wait!
95: Same.
95: This will be a wild adventure!
OS X Leopard: A new experience!
OS X Leopard: Indeed.
Vista: Same here.
Vista: I haven't really hiked before.
Chicago: Most of us haven’t, I think.
Chicago: I've only been
to Kernel.
3.1: Yeah, only except once.
Chicago: Oh, yeah.
95: We’ll be here for a day or so.
95: I’ve got some tents, by the way.
8: Ah, nice!
7: I actually like camping more.
7: Hotels aren't really my thing.
Vista: I prefer both.
Vista: Although I do like camping more.
95: Same.
95: Also, I figure we should eat our lunch first.
98: Good idea.
Chicago: Yeah, I'm hungry.
Chicago: Hmm, what about a picnic?
95: Yeah, I was thinking of that.
98: Hey, we’re here now!
95: Yep!
98: That was a fun ride.
Chicago: The journey isn’t over yet.
Chicago: We’re just getting started!
98: I agree.
98: Let's get going!